{
    "id": "11eb59e84fcb4320a2fe9632a81f9ec5",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I like …………………… music.",
            "description": "We cannot use every with uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every",
                "each"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You have eaten ……………………… loaf.",
            "description": "All is not normally used with a or an.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "all a",
                "a whole"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Under no circumstances ………………………… allowed in the pub.",
            "description": "We use an inverted word order after negative expressions like ‘under no circumstances’.",
            "answers": [
                "children are",
                "are children"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The two sisters are very much ……………………….",
            "description": "Alike means like each other. It is used in predicative positions.",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "alike",
                "similar"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was here a year ………………………….",
            "description": "We use ago to count back from the present.",
            "answers": [
                "ago",
                "before",
                "back"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… drug is 100 percent safe.",
            "description": "We cannot start a new sentence with not any. Instead we use no.",
            "answers": [
                "No",
                "Not any",
                "None of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I think we should paint the wall …………………….. color.",
            "description": "Another means an alternative.",
            "answers": [
                "an other",
                "another",
                "other"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am looking forward to being .................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "grandmother",
                "the grandmother",
                "a grandmother"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He has two children. …………………… of them are good at maths.",
            "description": "Both is used to speak of two people or things.",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "Both",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will be here ……………………. four o’clock onwards.",
            "description": "We do not use since to measure duration from the point of view of a future end-point.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will phone you when I …………………….. time.",
            "description": "In subordinate clauses, we normally use a present tense with a future meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "will have",
                "would have"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I had no sooner closed the door …………………….. somebody knocked.",
            "description": "We use than after sooner. ",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "when",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}